Veasna Phen

Information Technology

To establish and provide an effective, accessible system network for the benefit of the company & employee's daily tasks, case workload and meet deadlines of the company.

Enthusiastic and dedicated IT technician with experience of building/creating server and network of backup & storage, data processing and analysis, troubleshooting, test, and documentation reports. Offers a strong diagnostic skills and ability to immediately implement solution for system network failures. Passionate, hardworking, and fast learner with excellent interpersonal communication, adopt working environment, customer service, and office support skills

CONTACT

7212 200th ST CT E, Spanaway WA, 98387

253-576-6179/ 253-847-3622

Veasna.Phen@Hotmail.com

EDUCATION

Certification

ComPTIA A+ - 2017

Muckleshoot Tribal College/ WA, Auburn - 2015 – 2016

General SKILLS

- IT Technician
- Troubleshoot Computer hardware & Software
- In-home networking
- Critical Thinking
- Customer services
- Basic knowledge of LAN/WAN
- Communication
- Teamwork
- Basic Knowledge of IPv4/IPv6
- Basic knowledge of TCP/UDP protocol
- Beginner knowledge of active directory

$R\,E\,F\,E\,R\,E\,N\,C\,E\,S$

- Samantha Peterson 208-600-4726
- Bryan Shim

253 227-7382

Richard Lavietes
925 699-5260

Jay Choi

206-876-0200

EXPERIENCE

Position Title: Dell IT field

RMS Computer/ Boeing: Nov 2018 - March 2020

Job Description: A contract work for Boeing to provide IT support in person, and setup new devices for the user.

- Strong knowledge about computer peripherals
- Provide troubleshooting support for end user in person.
- Reimagine user's devices.
- Migrate user's data to the new device from the old device via USMT
- Deploying new devices to Boeing's employees

Position Title: PC Configuration

ESPO/Contract - Zones: July 2018 - October 2018

Job Description: Provide my technical skills to deploy devices, and computers for various companies such as Microsoft, TJX, Costco, Peace Health, etc.

- Utilize my troubleshooting skills on common issue of deployment.
- Building computers and replacing hardware.
- Configuration PC, printers, Devices, servers, and basic networking.
- Provide and following Quality Control protocol for the Deployment.
- Basic knowledge on Genetec security's active directory

Honda of Fife / 2016 - 2018

Job Description: Detail any vehicles that are from services and sale department

- Work at fast pace environment
- Detailing interior and exterior of the vehicles
- Utilizing ticket system

In-home Projects

- Troubleshoot Computers hardware and Software
- Build In-home network
- Configuring routers and Modem
- Optimizing and maintain windows OS
- Build multiple computers
- Custom Liquid Cooling
- Microsoft Hyper-V
- Computers deployment